traveldailynews.com 2006-06-23

# Untitled Document

Thank you for visiting TravelDailyNews.com, a Travel Media Applications' site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site.

  **The Information We Collect**

 At our site you may subscribe to our online newsletter. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number,country of origin, fax number, and information about your occupation and interests.

  **How We Use the Information**

 We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our services, to respond to your inquiries, and to offer you other information or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

 We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter.

 If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a "comment"), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us.

 We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage.

 We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.

 Agents and contractors of TravelDailyNews who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for TravelDailyNews.

 Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

 We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you.

 Finally, the TravelDailyNews site covered by this Privacy Notice will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

  **Our Commitment to Security**

 We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

  **Surveys**

 From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose any information requested. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving our services.

  **How to Contact Us**

 If you have any questions or concerns about the TravelDailynews online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [rania@traveldailynews.com.](mailto:rania@traveldailynews.com)

  **Updates & Effective Date**

 From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. 

 The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on or about December, 2004.
